<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<about>
    <personalinfo>
            <myname>Leif Linder</myname>
            <sted>
                <mycountry>NORWAY</mycountry>
                <myaddress>Olav Aukrust Vei 4C</myaddress>
                <mycity>Oslo</mycity>
                <mymobilephone>+47 46 901 863</mymobilephone>
            </sted>
            <sted>
                <mycountry>USA</mycountry>
                <myaddress> 3716 NE 57th</myaddress>
                <mycity> Seattle</mycity>
                <mymobilephone>206 330 4784</mymobilephone>
            </sted>
            <myemail>leif@leiflinder.com</myemail>
            <mylinkin>leiflinkin</mylinkin>
            <mygithub>leifgithub</mygithub>
    </personalinfo>
   <resumetexts>
        <intro>
        <p>Hello, my name is Leif Linder. I am a web developer from Seattle Washington but have lived all over the world. I studied Web Developing in New York and worked as on primarily PHP based web applications for many years.</p>
        <p>Although coding is my current professional I have worked in the stock photography business as an image researcher and supplier of images.</p>
        <p>My college education is in Media and writing for media and new writing. I am maninly professionally concerned with creating documents, whether that be as web code or images or news and journalism.</p>
        </intro>
        <freetime>
        <p>Hello, my name is Leif Linder. I am a web developer from Seattle Washington but have lived all over the world. I studied Web Developing in New York and worked as on primarily PHP based web applications for many years.</p>
        <p>Although coding is my current professional I have worked in the stock photography business as an image researcher and supplier of images.</p>
        <p>My college education is in Media and writing for media and new writing. I am maninly professionally concerned with creating documents, whether that be as web code or images or news and journalism.</p>
        </freetime>
        <personalitytype>
        INTP
        </personalitytype>
        <personality>
        <p>I am a highly creative person according to personality testing and rely heavily on intuition. I am mostly interested in the heavy subjects and am not great at small talk but can become quite passionate when talking about ideas or concepts.</p>
        <p>Although I have an INTP personality type I am not a cold nerd and I truly care about people's feelings. My empathy for people is high and I am concerned about the generally happiness of my workplace and maintaining personal communications by always treating my coworkers with respect. I don't gossip or create unwarranted drama.</p>
        </personality>
    </resumetexts>
    <goals>
        <p>sdfa sdfasdfasd fas fdasdfa sdfasdfas  asdf  sadf  s asd a</p>
        <p>sdfa sdfasdfasd fas fdasdfa sdfasdfas  asdf  sadf  s asd a</p>
        <p>sdfa sdfasdfasd fas fdasdfa sdfasdfas  asdf  sadf  s asd a</p>
    </goals>
</about>