<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<about>
    <personalinfo>
            <myname>Leif Linder</myname>
            <sted>
                <mycountry>USA</mycountry>
                <myaddress> 3716 NE 57th</myaddress>
                <mycity> Seattle</mycity>
                <mymobilephone>206 330 4784</mymobilephone>
            </sted>
            <sted>
                <mycountry>NORWAY</mycountry>
                <myaddress>Olav Aukrust Vei 4C</myaddress>
                <mycity>Oslo</mycity>
                <mymobilephone>+47 46 901 863</mymobilephone>
            </sted>
            <myemail>leif@leiflinder.com</myemail>
            <mylinkin>leiflinkin</mylinkin>
            <mygithub>leifgithub</mygithub>
    </personalinfo>
   <resumetexts>
        <intro>
        <p>Hello, my name is Leif Linder. I am a web developer from Seattle Washington but have lived all over the world. I studied Web Developing in New York and worked as on primarily PHP based web applications for many years.</p>
        <p>Although coding is my current professional I have worked in the stock photography business as an image researcher and supplier of images.</p>
        <p>My college education is in Media and writing for media and new writing. I am maninly professionally concerned with creating documents, whether that be as web code or images or news and journalism.</p>
        </intro>

        <freetime>
        <p>"Move through space and time" is something I say a lot. I really enjoy going places on my bike or bus or tram.</p>
        <p>I like to take the train  and I like to fly to different cities and learn their transit system.</p>
        <p>In one form or another I am always traveling. I am not a person who wants to lie on the beach or lounge at a spa. I always have to have action and adventure, when I am not working.</p> 
        </freetime>
    </resumetexts>
    <goals>
        <p>My goal is to develop my current ideas including a delivery app and a social media app for artists and musician. These are concrete goals although I also have less tangible goals.</p>
        <p>I would like to work in a place where we do something I am proud of and proud to be a part of. I want to work where my ability to be creative and design systems is valued. It would be great to work with relaxed and friendly people and to have a fun mix of worktime and creative time.</p>
    </goals>
</about>