<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<about>
    <personalinfo>
            <myname>Leif Linder</myname>
            <sted>
                <mycountry>USA</mycountry>
                <myaddress> 3716 NE 57th</myaddress>
                <mycity> Seattle</mycity>
                <mymobilephone>206 330 4784</mymobilephone>
            </sted>
            <sted>
                <mycountry>NORWAY</mycountry>
                <myaddress>Olav Aukrust Vei 4C</myaddress>
                <mycity>Oslo</mycity>
                <mymobilephone>+47 46 901 863</mymobilephone>
            </sted>
            <myemail>leif@leiflinder.com</myemail>
            <mylinkin>leiflinkin</mylinkin>
            <mygithub>leifgithub</mygithub>
    </personalinfo>
   <resumetexts>
        <intro>
        <p>Hello, my name is Leif Linder. I am a web developer and world citizen. Although I was born in Seattle my professional life started in New York City, first in stock and lifestyle photography and later in programming school and as a web developer.
        </p>
        <p>I have a long history in image making and expressive arts and have an emotional and creative personality that relies heavily on intuition a visual harmony. I love symmetry in design and code. I love the balance of design ethnic Ivory Coast masks, but also XML code and the nestes tags that describe not only the content but its relation with a complex.
        </p>
        <p>In this way I always looking for the rhythm of underlying systems, which means I start out slow. Slow to understand and slow to create. But will suddenly begin creating projects that win the support of directors. [see New York Road Runner Projects].
        </p>
        <p>I have the ability to see where trends are really going and the ability to verbalize and intangible and as-yet unrecognized concensus in the collective consciouness [see my predictions].</p>
        <p>My selling point is my vision. Not for everyone. Not for every job. I am not a machine. I feel and have feelings. I want to create applications that facilate the human species to evlove to higher spiritual planes. And to this end I know exactly what to do [See my current projects]</p>
        </intro>
        <freetime>
        <p>"Move through time and space" is something I am saying a lot lately. I like to spend my free riding through the city or getting on a train and going someplace interesting. I like moving and being outside early. I like activities where I am going someplace and feeling the wind in my face.</p> 
        <p>I also play guitar and run marathons.</p>

        </freetime>
        <personalitytype>
        INTP
        </personalitytype>
        <personality>
        <p>I am a highly creative person according to personality testing and rely heavily on intuition. I am mostly interested in the heavy subjects and am not great at small talk but can become quite passionate when talking about ideas or concepts.</p>
        <p>Although I have an INTP personality type I am not a cold nerd and I truly care about people's feelings. My empathy for people is high and I am concerned about the generally happiness of my workplace and maintaining personal communications by always treating my coworkers with respect. I don't gossip or create unwarranted drama.</p>
        </personality>
    </resumetexts>
    <goals>
        <p>My current goal is to be working with a team of developers creating really interesting digital products.</p>
        <p>I want to be part of something I find both artistically challenging and fullfiling. And I want to collaborate with people who recognise my odd genius and be kindred spirirts</p>
    </goals>
</about>