<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<codelist>
    <code>
        <codetitle>PHP</codetitle>
        <codeid>1001</codeid>
        <description>
I am able to create fully developed web applications with PHP. I use objected oriented design principles and buid MVC systems for web sites. My history using PHP is long but I am most proud of my recent project. See GitHub for my work.
        </description>
        <github>https://github.com/LeifLinder/</github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>Angular 2</codetitle>
        <codeid>1002</codeid>
        <description>
I have a good understanding of client-side Javasript frameworks and experience building AngularJS websites (see GitHub). I can use a model-view-controller framework and have working knowledge of Angular directives, filters and controllers. I can build single page applications using AngularJS, in addition to setting up a RESTful server.
        </description>
        <github>https://github.com/LeifLinder/</github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>CSS</codetitle>
        <codeid>1003</codeid>
        <description>
        With CSS I can build stylesheets that are logical and easy to understand and update. I use SASS preprocessor for the convenience of variables and mixins and to avoid code redundancy.
        </description>
        <github>https://github.com/LeifLinder/</github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>HTML</codetitle>
        <codeid>1004</codeid>
        <description>
        I can build pages without consulting the web to remember the tags. In all my pages I try to follow symantic principles and ofter turn off style to see how the browser really sees the page. Also. Am up-to-date with HTML5 special tags.
        </description>
        <github>https://github.com/LeifLinder/</github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>Javascript</codetitle>
        <codeid>1005</codeid>
        <description>
        I can write vanilla Javascript without needing to look up basics task like creating arrays or variables or interating through sets. I can additioanly build Angular2 and ReactJS sites and jQuery assets.
        </description>
        <github>https://github.com/LeifLinder/</github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>MySQL</codetitle>
        <codeid>1006</codeid>
        <description>
        I have several years experience creating basic queries and joining tables by row ids on select values. I can normalize databases to not dubplicate values and am able to create logical table schema for ease of mantainence and information retrieval.
        </description>
        <github>https://github.com/LeifLinder/</github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>XML XSLT</codetitle>
        <codeid>1007</codeid>
        <description>
        I am able to build XML documents that indentify content types and conform to associated stylesheets. I can also transform documents to HTML or use as datasets in PHP or Javascript applications.
        </description>
        <github>https://github.com/LeifLinder/</github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>Drupal</codetitle>
        <codeid>1008</codeid>
        <description>
        I have a lot of professional experience using early versions of Drupal 5, 6, 7. I can build Drupal websites and create custom themes and define users and control their access by role. Please see examples of my work.
        </description>
        <github>https://github.com/LeifLinder/</github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>Illustrator</codetitle>
        <codeid>1009</codeid>
        <description>
        please see my designs. I have a good working knowledge of Illustrator and geniunely enjoy building art and mockups.
        </description>
        <github></github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>Bootstrap</codetitle>
        <codeid>1010</codeid>
        <description>
       Bootstrap is my favorite framework and I use it every day. I stay educated and often consult bootstrap wedsite to learn particulars of inline and block level elements and how to leverage the grid system. With monbile-first design I can easily build for every device but can also change styles with custom stylesheet.
        </description>
        <github></github>
    </code>

    <code>
        <codetitle>Photoshop</codetitle>
        <codeid>1013</codeid>
        <description>
        I am no pro but I can use Photoshop adequately with layers and the most common functions, removing background altering colors, clean up image, etc.
        </description>
        <github></github>
    </code>

    <code>
        <codetitle>Linux</codetitle>
        <codeid>1019</codeid>
        <description>
        Ubuntu is my flavor of linux and I am fully capabale of navigating the server via the command line and installing software and other tasks.
        </description>
        <github></github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>Apache</codetitle>
        <codeid>1020</codeid>
        <description>
        With apached I can create virtual domains and configure security and other necessary attitubes for domain handling, PHP and other aspects.
        </description>
        <github></github>
    </code>
    <code>
        <codetitle>JAVA</codetitle>
        <codeid>1021</codeid>
        <description>
        I love JAVA and have taken many classes, array and array lists. I can build good classes and create and iterate arrays. I am not a professional but have a solid understanding and deep appreciation for Object Oriented programming with this noble language.
        </description>
        <github></github>
    </code>
</codelist>
