<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resume>

    <personalinfo>
            <myname>Leif Linder</myname>
            <sted>
                <mycountry>NORWAY</mycountry>
                <mycity>Oslo</mycity>
                <mymobilephone>+47 46 901 863</mymobilephone>
            </sted>
            <sted>
                <mycountry>USA</mycountry>
                <mycity> Seattle</mycity>
                <mymobilephone>206 330 4784</mymobilephone>
            </sted>
            <myemail>leif@leiflinder.com</myemail>
            <mylinkin>leiflinkin</mylinkin>
            <mygithub>leifgithub</mygithub>
    </personalinfo>

    <resumetexts>
        <intro>
        <p>Hello, my name is Leif Linder. I am a web developer from Seattle Washington but have lived all over the world. I studied Web Developing in New York and worked as on primarily PHP based web applications for many years.</p>
        <p>Although coding is my current professional I have worked in the stock photography business as an image researcher and supplier of images.</p>
        <p>My college education is in Media and writing for media and new writing. I am maninly professionally concerned with creating documents, whether that be as web code or images or news and journalism.</p>
        </intro>
        <personalitytype>
        INTP
        </personalitytype>
        <personality>
        <p>I am a highly creative person according to personality testing and rely heavily on intuition. I am mostly interested in the heavy subjects and am not great at small talk but can become quite passionate when talking about ideas or concepts.</p>
        <p>Although I have an INTP personality type I am not a cold nerd and I truly care about people's feelings. My empathy for people is high and I am concerned about the generally happiness of my workplace and maintaining personal communications by always treating my coworkers with respect. I don't gossip or create unwarranted drama.</p>
        </personality>
    </resumetexts>
    <jobs>
        <job>
            <jobid>1001</jobid>
            <jobtitle>Industrial Athlete</jobtitle>
            <joblocation>Oslo, Norway</joblocation>
            <jobstart>November 2016</jobstart>
            <jobstartyear>2016</jobstartyear>
            <jobfinish>September 2019</jobfinish>
            <jobfinishyear>2019</jobfinishyear>
            <companyname>Foodora AS</companyname>
            <companyaddress>Olso Norway</companyaddress>
            <jobdescription>Martian Rocket</jobdescription>
        </job>
        <job>
            <jobid>1002</jobid>
            <jobtitle>Manager, Digital Integration and Design</jobtitle>
            <companyname>New York Road Runners</companyname>
            <joblocation>New York, New York</joblocation>
            <jobstart>October 2012</jobstart>
            <jobstartyear>2012</jobstartyear>
            <jobfinish>September 2015</jobfinish>
            <jobfinishyear>2015</jobfinishyear>
            <jobdescription>
            As Web Manager and PHP developer I maintained and extended two large drupal websites, compiled user analytics and improved SEO. I coded dozens of single page websites, kiosk portals and full custom PHP CMS systems and while communicating regularly with project managers and developers overseas.
            </jobdescription>
        </job>
        <job>
            <jobid>1003</jobid>
            <jobtitle>Web Developer</jobtitle>
            <companyname>StarPoint Solutions</companyname>
            <joblocation>New York, New York</joblocation>
            <jobstart>2011</jobstart>
            <jobstartyear>2011</jobstartyear>
            <jobfinish>2012</jobfinish>
            <jobfinishyear>2012</jobfinishyear>
            <jobdescription>
            Built HTML pages for New York Road Runners, New York City Marathon. Built PHP Sweepstakes web applications for runners to win entry.
            </jobdescription>
        </job>
        <job>
            <jobid>1004</jobid>
            <jobtitle>Web Developer</jobtitle>
            <companyname>McFadden Media Inc</companyname>
            <joblocation>New York, New York</joblocation>
            <jobstart>2009</jobstart>
            <jobstartyear>2009</jobstartyear>
            <jobfinish>2010</jobfinish>
            <jobfinishyear>2010</jobfinishyear>
            <jobdescription>
            I built three drupal websites for McFadden Media. Point Magazine, Dance Teacher News and Dance Retailer News. In addition I created an internal website for employees use.
            </jobdescription>
        </job>
    </jobs>
    <skills>
        <skill>
            <skilltitle>
            PHP
            </skilltitle>
            <skilldescription>
            I have a good command of the PHP components including variables, arrays, loops, and datatypes. I use object-oriented design principles on my projects. I have built many small scale web applications, (See Examples) and Drupal webites. 
            </skilldescription>
            <skillexamples>
            PHP examples here
            </skillexamples>
        </skill>
        <skill>
            <skilltitle>
            MySQL
            </skilltitle>
            <skilldescription>
          As a utility towards for accessing and creating data I can easily write complex queries with joins on tables (examples). I am not however, a database professional and have little experience optimizing for speed or other more complex actions.
            </skilldescription>
            <skillexamples>
            mysql examples link
            </skillexamples>
        </skill>
        <skill>
            <skilltitle>
            CSS
            </skilltitle>
            <skilldescription>
            My old friend CSS has been a buggy bedfellow but a friend too and I have much hard-earned experience solving difficult style solutions. I have a firm understand of CSS selectivity rules and can create simple but elegant stylesheets. I do use SASS variables but rarely create anything complex enough to take full advantage of preprocessors. 
            </skilldescription>
            <skillexamples>
            Examples of CSS and SASS
            </skillexamples>
        </skill>
        <skill>
            <skilltitle>
            Bootstrap
            </skilltitle>
            <skilldescription>
            Currently I use Bootstrap for my web projects and enjoy collecting templates. I have several costum designs that I can offer for Bootstrap image gallery or blog style or for creating forms that are simple and easy to understand. I enjoy studying the Bootsrap website for depicting lists and cards that adjst elegantly to the viewing device.
            </skilldescription>
            <skillexamples>
            Examples of CSS and SASS
            </skillexamples>
        </skill>
        <skill>
            <skilltitle>
            MISC
            </skilltitle>
            <skilldescription>
            Here are skills I have experience with or are learning now. 
            </skilldescription>
            <skillexamples>
            Examples of CSS and SASS
            </skillexamples>
        </skill>
    </skills>
    <goals>
        <goal>
        I want to design applications that connect people by psychology
        </goal>
        <goal>
        I want to provide modern services like Uber or Foodora or other apps using location
        </goal>
    </goals>
    <achievments>
      <achievment>
      Marathon Entertainment App
      </achievment>
    <achievment>
      Race Information App
      </achievment>
    <achievment>
      Tomato220 time management
      </achievment>
    </achievments>
</resume>


